citibank.co.jp 1999-04-21

# Citibank Privacy Policy

Welcome to Citibank's Web site. This section explains our policy regarding any personal information you might supply to us when you visit this site. Our goal is to protect your information on the Internet in the same way that we protect it in all the other ways we interact with you: in branches, at ATMs, and on the phone. (You can also read "Citibank's Global Customer Privacy Promise", which outlines in more detail our privacy policy throughout Citibank.) 

**Citibank's Internet Privacy Policy**

  1. You can visit this site and find out about our products and services, read our Corporate reports, check on career opportunities, or get a news update and other value-added services without giving us any information about yourself. 
  2. If you do provide personal information, such as address, e-mail, telephone and fax numbers, as well as demographic and customer identification, we will not disclose (share, sell or divulge) it to third parties without your consent. We will maintain this information, as well as your business activities and transactions, according to our usual strict security and confidentiality standards. 

In order to provide better service, or to address security hazards, we will occasionally use a "cookie". A cookie is a small piece of information which a Web site stores on your Web browser on your PC and can later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by a Web site other than the one that set the cookie. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes, for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our site. Most cookies last only through a single session, or visit. None will contain information that will enable anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or "snail mail". You can set up your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set.
